(Sheldon:)with no semantic content at all?
(Penny:)My mirth. Classic.
(Sheldon:)Is there a station
coming up
(Sheldon:)where I can board your
giggling train of thought?
(Penny:)It's not a big deal, Sheldon.
(Penny:)It's just,
ever since Leonard's been
(Penny:)dating Raj's sister,
I've had to keep my distance.
(Penny:)I don't get to hear
all your jibber-jabber.
Jibber-jabber?!
(Sheldon:)I don't jibber-jabber.
(Penny:)What are you doing
at work these days?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm working on
time-dependent backgrounds
(Sheldon:)in string theory,
(Sheldon:)specifically quantum
field theory
in "d-dimensional"
de Sitter space.
Okay, come on, even you have
to admit that's jibber-jabber.
(Sheldon:)Interesting, do you know
(Sheldon:)where the phrase
"jibber-jabber" comes from?
(Howard:)Oh, my God,
you're about to jibber-jabber
(Penny:)about jibber-jabber.
(Leonard:)Howard and his mother
are at the hospital.
(Leonard:)- Come on, we gotta go.
- Oh, my God! What happened?
(Leonard:)I don't know, I just got a text.
Come on, hurry.
(Howard(reading a text):)Okay.